

taylorradtke@gmail.com | www.taylorradtke.com | (804) 929 - 7374Alexandria, VA

## SKILLS

### W3C Validated HTML5

#### BEM/CSS3 via Sass

Bourbon / Neat Foundation Skeleton Bootstrap

## JavaScript, ES6

Ember jQuery Babel React Gatsby Node.js

Vue

## PHP, Wordpress

Theme Development Advanced Custom Fields Admin/Plugin Setup SQL Management **Custom Functionality** Inheritance Model

# Web Design

UI/UX Design Sketching Interaction Design Grid & Layout Wireframing Color Theory Rapid Prototyping Typography Usability Graphic Design

# EDUCATION

## **2015 - PRESENT**

## General Assembly

Front-End Development Alexandria, VA

## 2011 - 2014

# Virginia Commonwealth University

Information Systems Alexandria, VA

## 2009 - 2011

# J. Sargeant Reynolds

Business (A.A.S) Richmond, VA

## ABOUT ME

Taylor Radtke is a creative mind who specializes in minimal design that displays a bold message. After three plus years of marketing in the service industry, Taylor takes his social skills mastered from constructing cocktails through college to create a finished project that his client truly loves. Taylor has a great latitude of culture due to his upbringing in Southern California, before transitioning to the mid-Atlantic region to further his career and education. He is passionate about web-design as a functional piece of art, and strive to let his mind continue to peruse the beauty of the digital experience.

## EXPERIENCE

## JULY 2018 - APRIL 2019

# Cisco Engineer

Herndon, VA

## OCT 2016 – JULY 2018

## AAPA

Full-Stack Web Developer Alexandria, VA

## APR 2016 - OCT 2016

The Motley Fool Front-End Web Developer

Completely redesigned website in under 4 months, on a new CMS.

Created a completely dynamic Wordpress Theme used by hundreds

of different partners that brands all pages and components with

their personal branding (Typography, brand colors, logo, etc)

Developed web site mock-ups for clients to ensure quality control and client satisfaction before project development phase. Lead Designer and Developer for Annual Conference Site.

Alexandria, VA

Developed and designed microsites, newsletters. Developed and designed, and e-mail templates. Conducted BrowserStack usability testing for pages on all devices.

## NOV 2015 - APR 2016

Total Wine & More Digital Media Designer

Bethesda, MD

Responsible for designing and maintaining web banners in various formats to be displayed on any device. Conducted analyses using Google Analytics and Google AdWords.

# AWARDS / CERTIFICATIONS

Green Belt Security Certified

White Belt Security Certified

Spot Award, 50th Landing Page

AAPA - 2017

Cisco - 2018

Cisco - 2018